

Contacts

Velikiy Novgorod, Russia
muricorabota@yandex.ru
murikuk.com
linkedin.com/in/murad-kukuev

Specialization

Web Design & Development
Brand Identity & Strategy
Search Engine Optimization
Web Content & Creative Writing

Languages

Russian (Native)
English (Professional Working)
Italian (Professional Working)
German (Elementary)

Murad Kukuev

General information

My profession is to create beautiful and reliable websites, and if you need a high-quality and full-fledged website - contact me. Experience 5 years - participated in the creation of a large number of sites.

In my work I use the following tools and languages: WordPress, HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL, JavaScript, Python, Java...

I have experience working in a team. I appreciate responsibility and reliability in people, in work - quality.

Married, have 2 children. I like to read books, play guitar, listen to music.

Experience

"Murico" - Head & Web Design Specialist

February 2016 - Present

Velikiy Novgorod (Russia)

"Novgorod Metallurgical Plant" - Engineer for design and estimate work

April 2012 - January 2016

Velikiy Novgorod (Russia)

Education

Dagestan State Technical University

Master of Science - MS, Hydraulic engineer · (1992 - 1998)

Makhachkala (Russia)

High School # 13

Graduate · (1982 - 1992)

Makhachkala (USSR)